你们想倒打一耙吗
Are you trying to turn this around on me?
这还不止  奥林
That's not all, Orrin.
还有你的地役权为了使用自己土地的便利而使用他人土地的权利
Your easement.
你看  山麓电网每隔几年
You see, every couple of years the Piedmont Electric,
就申请让输电线横穿加夫尼
they apply to bring power lines through Gaffney.
你这块地正好在路线之上
The route comes right through your lot.
我和吉恩每次都把这事压下
Now, Gene and I always fight them off.
但今年  他们要是再来申请
But this year, if they were to reapply, hmm...
政府强制征收
Eminent domain.
拆掉这么漂亮的房子  真是可惜
It would be such a shame to have to tear down this beautiful home.
见鬼去吧  弗兰克
Fuck you, Frank.
你休想跑到我家来  还一副你的地盘的样子
You can't just roll up on my property and act like you own it.
不  我可以
Oh, but I can.